locowise.com 2018-10-20

# Privacy Policy | Locowise

### Privacy policy

LocoWise Ltd wants you to understand how we use, protect and share information gathered while using our website and/or applications we offer. We're here to use data gathered for good, not evil. If you want to make sure we're not doing something you don't want us to do, email us at [support@locowise.com](mailto:support@locowise.com?Subject=Locowise%20Privacy%20Policy%20Enquiry).

### PROTECTING CHILDREN

As of April 21, 2000 the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act became effective. The regulations apply to the online collection of personal information from children under the age of 13. LocoWise Ltd is very sensitive to the issue of children's privacy and makes every effort to protect the privacy of children using the Internet. If you are under 13 years of age you should not use this website, and under no circumstances should you send information about yourself to LocoWise Ltd, this Web site, products, and services are not developed for or directed at children. Our policy is not to permit anyone under the age of 18 to do business with us. If LocoWise Ltd discovers that a child under the age of 13 has provided LocoWise Ltd with personally identifiable information, LocoWise Ltd will immediately delete that child's personally identifiable information from the website.

### WHAT TYPES OF INFORMATION DOES LOCOWISE LTD COLLECT AND HOW WILL IT BE USED?

LocoWise Ltd only collects information from you on a voluntary basis. We do not send Spam or sell email addresses. So that we can provide you with the most efficient and enhanced experience, we request that you register for a personal account accessible through a confidential password and screen name that you select. For purposes of registration, we collect identifiable information about you such as your name, email address, and demographic information such as age, gender and zip code. We also may collect your IP address, browser type, operating system type, domain name, access times and referring website address. This information is collecting during registration or in response to specific requests from you, for things such as signing up for an email newsletter, chat room, or other online information service we may offer, entering a contest, answering a survey, or contacting us. Surveys are conducted strictly for internal profiling purposes and only keep track of anonymous demographic data (e.g., your age, usage of the LocoWise Ltd website, favorite features).

Our website contains links through which an online user can email us. We collect personal information contained in the email for the purpose of responding to a user's questions and/or comments. From time to time, we may post on our website job openings at LocoWise Ltd and provide an email address to which interested applicants can submit their resume. Although we can assure you that any personal information contained in a resume will be used solely for its intended purpose (i.e., to evaluate the applicant's qualifications), such information is not subject to this privacy policy. No matter what method we use to collect information and no matter how we use that information, we will only collect the information deemed reasonably necessary to fulfill your online requests and our legitimate business objectives.

### DOES LOCOWISE LTD USE COOKIES OR OTHER MEANS TO COLLECT INFORMATION?

We may collect some information about you by using data collection technology, it may not be readily apparent to you when data is being collected. For instance, when you come to our website, your IP address is collected so that we know where to send information you are requesting. An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet. A "cookie" is a small file or record-keeping device that websites often store on a user's computer. (You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer.) This information may be used to make our website more interesting and useful to you. Additionally, we may combine this information with personally identifiable information to identify a user in order to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use or to protect our service, website or users of LocoWise Ltd's website.

### WITH WHOM DOES LOCOWISE LTD SHARE MY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?

LocoWise Ltd reserves the right to use your company name, logo and other identifiable marks for any and all promotional purposes. If you do not wish to have you company name or mark used by LocoWise Ltd you must opt-out by notifying us in writing: please contact us via email at [support@locowise.com](mailto:support@locowise.com?Subject=Locowise%20Privacy%20Policy%20Enquiry). LocoWise Ltd will take reasonable care in removing your name or mark within a reasonable time.

From time to time, we may employ and share your personal information with vendors who use it solely to provide support for the internal operations of our website (e.g., technical support and network delivery). These entities will not use your personally identifiable information for any other purpose, and have agreed to maintain the confidentiality, security, and integrity of the personal information they obtain from us.

It is our policy not to share, sell or rent your personal information to any company not directly related to LocoWise Ltd. LocoWise Ltd reserves the right to share your personally identifiable information with our parent or affiliated companies. Further, LocoWise Ltd may sell, transfer or otherwise disclose user information, including personally identifiable information, in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, the sale of substantially all assets, or other fundamental corporate change. We may disclose your personal information in the good faith belief that we are required to do so by law or to comply with legal processes, respond to any claims or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of LocoWise Ltd staff or the public.

### THIRD PARTY ADVERTISEMENTS AND CONTENT

When you are using the LocoWise Ltd website, certain content, including advertisements, may be created or hosted by a third party. Such third parties may place cookies and/or use web beacons, which may be used to identify some of your preferences or to recognize you if you have previously had contact with them. We do not control the use of such technology by third parties, the information they collect, or how they use such information. LocoWise Ltd does not disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties serving ads or other content on our website.

### WHAT IS LOCOWISE LTD'S POLICY REGARDING LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES?

You should be aware that while you are on a website operated by us, you may be directed to links to other websites. The privacy policies of these other websites are beyond our control and we take no responsibility for their practices. Because we cannot guarantee that the privacy of these websites meet our high standards, we recommend that you read the privacy policy of the website to which you link before you submit any personal information.

### HOW CAN I GAIN ACCESS TO OR AMEND MY PERSONAL INFORMATION? (GDPR REQUESTS FOR ACCESS)

If you wish to review, update, or delete any personal information that we may have collected about you, please contact us via email at [support@locowise.com](mailto:support@locowise.com?Subject=Locowise%20Privacy%20Policy%20Enquiry). You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. So if you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email or write to us at the following address. We will never charge you for this service. We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.

The [General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)](https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/) is a vitally important part of ensuring absolute transparency between companies like ourselves at Locowise, and our valued application users, who depend on us every day to measure and report on their social media performance.

The GDPR supersedes the 1995 Data Protection Directive. One of the most prominent changes, being that even if a company operates outside of the EU, regulation applies to how those companies market their products and services to EU citizens. All users of Locowise have the right to submit a complaint to the ICO you are unsure about how LocoWise Ltd is handling your personal data.

### HOW LONG IS MY DATA RETAINED BY LOCOWISE?

LocoWise Ltd will keep all subscribed client personal data (including First Name, Surname and Email Address) of each client team member until such time we are instructed to remove a client team member or unsubscribe an account from LocoWise. You can do this by talking to us in real time at Locowise.com, selecting the livechat symbol in the bottom right hand corner of your screen or by emailing your request for access.

LocoWise Ltd will keep all unsubscribed (free trial) user personal data (including First Name, Surname and Email Address) for a standard retention period of up to 24 months. We do this in order to keep you up to date with the latest industry trends and insights via our blog newsletter (which you can opt out of at any time).

### WHAT ARE MY PRIVACY RIGHTS IF I AM LOCATED OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA?

LocoWise Ltd makes an effort to protect the personally identifiable information of all users of its website. We attempt to comply with local data protection and consumer rights laws to the extent they may apply to LocoWise Ltd's services. If you are uncertain whether this privacy policy conflicts with the applicable local privacy laws where you are located, you should not submit your personally identifiable information to LocoWise Ltd. If you are located within the European Union, you should be aware that your personally identifiable information will be transferred to the United States of America, the laws of which may be deemed by the European Union to have inadequate data protection. If you are located in a country outside the United States of America and voluntarily submit personally identifiable information to us, you thereby consent to the general use of such information as provided in this privacy policy and to the transfer of that information to, and/or storage of that information in, the United States of America.

### CHANGES IN THE LOCOWISE LTD PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time. If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our website so that you and other users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. You should also check back from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes.

### SECURITY

LocoWise Ltd takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. When you enter sensitive information, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). LocoWise Ltd also has an internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of customer and other data, limiting access only to those employees who we reasonably believe need to know such information for the purpose of performing their jobs. The Internet is not a 100% secure medium. Although we use reasonable efforts to protect information, the potential of somebody breaching our security measures does exist.

By using this website, you signify your assent to the LocoWise Ltd Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this privacy policy, please do not use this website or applications. Your continued use of this website or applications will signify your acceptance of these changes.
